x2crm.com 2017-03-01

# X2CRM Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Effective Date: May 1, 2015

This Privacy Policy covers X2Engine.com and X2CRM.com websites (hereinafter “Website”), which is owned

and operated by X2Engine, Inc. (“X2Engine”). X2Engine is committed to protecting the privacy of

its users and wishes to maintain a safe and secure environment for all users of the Website.

Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your personal information is treated.

From time to time, X2Engine may offer new services and/or products that may require X2Engine

to update this Privacy Policy. Please check back with us periodically. If you have questions or

concerns regarding this statement, you should contact the X2Engine’s Privacy Administrator by

email at privacy@x2engine.com.

This Privacy Policy answers the following questions for you regarding your online privacy

protection:

WHAT INFORMATION DOES X2ENGINE COLLECT?

X2Engine collects personal information from users for different purposes.  Information gathered

online can be identified as either anonymous or identifiable.  Anonymous information is

information that cannot be traced back to the individual.  Identifiable information is information

that is specific to an individual.

Anonymous Information

Like many sites, the Website gathers certain information automatically and stores it.  This

information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, searches performed, browser types,

Internet services providers (ISP), referring/exit pages, date/time stamps, and clickstream data.

X2Engine uses this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends

administer the Website, gather demographic information about its user base as a whole, and

improve its level of service to you. X2Engine does not link this automatically-collected data to

personally identifiable information.

Personally Identifiable Information

To obtain a free trial and/or to purchase X2Engine’s products or to use the community forums, a

user must register for an account. To create an account, a user must complete an online form.

Through the form, X2Engine collects one or more of the following items of information as

indicated on the form: (i) name, (ii) email address, (iii) address, (iv) phone number, (v) credit card

information, (vi) username, and (vii) password. To the extent financial data is not collected to

create an account, financial data may be collected through a separate online form or through a

third party payment processor in order to finalize and complete a transaction.

DOES THE WEBSITE USE “COOKIES”?

Yes, the Website uses cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s device to help us

improve your access to the Website and identify repeat visitors. Cookies can also enable us to

track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on the Website. Cookies

are not linked to any personally identifiable information.

HOW DOES X2ENGINE USE MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

Personally identifiable information collected is used primarily for the purpose it is collected (e.g.,

creating a user account). X2Engine also may use a user’s email address and/or phone number

as follows provided that the user grants his/her consent to such additional use:

  * in our internal surveys to obtain feedback on the Website or on other aspects of our
  * business;
  * to notify users of information we think may be of interest to them; and
  * to send communications or promotional materials.

We may also use personal information collected to contact users in connection with the

inappropriate use of the Website.

DOES X2ENGINE DISCLOSE MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

From time to time, X2Engine may disclose your personal information to organizations that

perform services for or on behalf of X2Engine, for example to provide customer service, for

research, marketing, payment processing, credit checks, data processing, and to measure the

use of our Website. We will share with these companies only that personal information which

they need to work on our behalf. Some of these service providers may be located in other

countries. Your personal information will be provided to these organizations only if they agree to

use such information solely for the purpose of providing services to X2Engine, and under the

instructions of X2Engine, and with respect to that information, to act in a manner consistent with

the relevant principles articulated in this Privacy Policy.

IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?

The Website has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the

information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any

such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

CAN I UPDATE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT ME?

You have the right to correct and update the personal information collected about you through the

Website. You can make changes to your personal information at any time by logging into your

account. You will need your username and password in order to access your account.

WILL YOU NOTIFY ME IN THE EVENT OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY?

X2Engine reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. In the event of a material

change in our information collection and handling practices, X2Engine will inform those users who

have provided an email address via email. Any changes will apply prospectively only.

HOW CAN I OPT-OUT FROM RECEIVING EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS?

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used

for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you register for an account

but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your

preference during the account creation process. If you opted-in to receive marketing

communications but no longer wish to receive communications from us, you may opt-out of

receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication.

LINKS

The Website may contain links to other sites or Websites. Please be aware that X2Engine is not

responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites or Websites. We

encourage users to read the privacy policies of each and every site or Website that collects

personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by

the Website.

NOTICE REGARDING CHILDREN

The X2Engine Website is general audience Website and does not direct any of its content

specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting

the sensitive nature of children’s privacy. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a user is

under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user’s account.

INTERNATIONAL USERS

X2Engine is a U.S. company and the Website is hosted in the United States. If you access the

Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region, country, or jurisdiction with privacy

laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United

States privacy laws, please note that, by your continued use of the Website, you are transferring

your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. In addition, you

understand that your personal information may be processed in countries (including the United

States) where privacy laws may be less stringent than in your country.

HOW DO I CONTACT X2ENGINE ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS?

If you have any further questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us

at privacy@x2engine.com.

REQUIRED DISCLOSURES

X2Engine may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that

such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal

process served on our site.
